rasputeen.net 2010-01-31

# Privacy Policy : SafetyBilling

**

Privacy Policy Statement

**

This website (the "site") is licensed to SinComm Limited.

Our postal address is  
Strovolou, 77 Strovolos Center Flat/Office 204  
Nicosia 2018 Cyprus 

We can be reached via e-mail at [privacy-1@silvercash.com](mailto:privacy-1@silvercash.com)

This Privacy Policy Statement sets forth the policies and practices with respect to information or data gathered regarding subscriber and members of this site. This is an adult site that expressly and strictly limits its membership to adults. All persons under the age of 18 are strictly prohibited from accessing or viewing the contents of this site.

This site does not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons under the age of 18.

Notice - Use of website by the subscriber constitutes the subscriber's express assent to the use of personal information collected by site.

CAREFULLY READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT BECAUSE BY YOUR SUBSCRIPTION TO AND USE OF THIS SITE YOU WILL BE EXPRESSLY SIGNIFYING THAT YOU AGREE TO THIS POLICY STATEMENT AND THAT YOU ASSENT TO THE USE OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT YOU SUPPLY OR THAT IS COLLECTED ABOUT YOU AS DETAILED IN THIS POLICY STATEMENT.

IF YOU DO NOT EXPRESSLY AGREE WITH ALL OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT YOU SHOULD NOT SUBSCRIBE TO OR USE THIS SITE.

 _ **What Information About Subscribers is Collected?**_

When any adult consumer signs-on as a member or subscriber of this site that consumer will be required to provide certain personal as well as demographic information which includes the subscriber's name, e-mail address, zip code, country, username, and password. This site collects any and all such information and includes it in its customer database.

If the site features or conducts any special events, special promotions or offers, contests or polls, a subscriber of the site may be asked to provide information in order to participate, if the subscriber voluntarily provides that information, all such information may be collected by the site and included in its customer database.

If a subscriber sends any personal communication or correspondence, by any means, to the site, or any of its employees, agents or representatives, the site may collect any information regarding that communication and include that information in its customer database.

The site may also automatically collect traffic and click-through data as well as information regarding the online behavior of subscribers by the use of "cookies" or other programming means - any information about subscribers collected by the site through the use of cookies or other programming means will generally not be associable to the specific user in any way.

You may obtain further information about "cookies" and how they function at: <http://www.cookiecentral.com/>.

 _ **Use of Personal Subscriber Information.**_

By the subscriber's use of the site, the subscriber expressly agrees that the site may use any personal information that has been provided by the subscriber or that has been collected by the site about the subscriber for any purpose, including without limitation, technical, administration, research and development, customer administration, marketing, trading in personal data, age verification, promotional and advertising use by the site or third parties authorized to use the information by the site.

By the subscriber's use of the site, the subscriber expressly agrees that the site may, in its sole discretion share, disclose, transfer, rent, license or sell any of the personal information about subscribers that it has gathered or collected with affiliated or unaffiliated third parties.

Please note that personal information about a subscriber may be collected by a third-party web service provider that has an advertising banner or link on the site.

The site is not responsible or liable for the use of any information that a subscriber may provide, or that is gathered by third-party websites that have banner ads or links on the site. This site does not control, monitor or endorse the information gathering practices or privacy policies of any of those third-party websites.

Whenever applicable, each subscriber should seek to read the privacy policy of any third-party website provider that has an advertising banner, advertises or has a link on the site.

 _ **Security of Personal Information Collected by the site.**_

Consistent with the policies set forth in this privacy statement, the site has adopted and implemented reasonable and technologically feasible procedures for maintaining the security, accuracy and integrity of all personal information relating to subscribers that is collected by the site.

All subscribers should consider any information provided to or collected by the site as **non-confidential** , and consequently the site assumes no liability or responsibility if any information relating to any subscriber is intercepted and/or used by an unintended recipient.

 _ **"OPT-IN" and "OPT-OUT" Provisions.**_

There may be occasions when a subscriber will be presented with special offers either from the operators of the site or from third-party service or content providers, which may include consent to receive e-mail solicitations, communications, newsletters, commercial advertising, or other promotional or special event materials (collectively referred to as "Offers").

"OPT-IN" -- Some offers may be presented to the subscriber with the option to express the subsciber's preference by either clicking or entering "accept" (alternatively "yes") or "decline" (alternatively "no"). By selecting or clicking the "accept" or "yes" the subscriber indicates that the subscriber "OPTS-IN" to that offer and thereby agrees and assents that the subscriber's personal information and data may be disclosed to third-parties.

"OPT-OUT" -- Other offers may be presented with a pre-selected preference or choice. If the subscriber does not deselect the pre-selected preference of choice (i.e. "OPT-OUT" of the offer) then the site may transfer the subscriber's personal profile information to the third-party service or content provider making the offer. If the subscriber deselects the pre-selected preference then no personal information about the subscriber may be disclosed to any third-party service or content provider.

 _ **"OPT-OUT" Revocation Procedure.**_ The site also offers all subscribers a procedure for "Opting-Out" if the subscriber subsequently chooses to revoke any consent to receive offers by sending an e-mail to [privacy-1@silvercash.com](mailto:privacy-1@silvercash.com), clearly stating that the subscriber has revoked consent to receive any future offers. _ **Data Controller.**_

The Data Controller for all personal information collected about subscribers of the site can be reached by e-mail at [privacy-1@silvercash.com](mailto:privacy-1@silvercash.com). The Data Controller has the authority to resolve all issues regarding the collection, modification, correction, deletion and use of the personal information that has been collected by the site.

 _ **Review of Personal Information by Subscriber/Means of Challenging Data.**_

A subscriber to this site can review any personal information collected by the site relating to that subscriber by sending an e-mail to the site's DATA CONTROLLER at [privacy-1@silvercash.com](mailto:privacy-1@silvercash.com), clearly stating that the subscriber wishes to review the subscriber's personal information which has been collected by the site.

The individual subscriber shall have the following rights with respect to any personal information gathered by the site:

  * to obtain from a data controller, or otherwise, confirmation of whether or not the data controller has data relating to him;  

  * to have communicated to him, data relating to him within a reasonable time; at a charge, if any, that is not excessive; in a reasonable manner; and in a form that is readily intelligible to him;  

  * to be given reasons if a request made under subparagraphs(a) and (b) is denied, and to be able to challenge such denial; and  

  * to challenge data relating to him and, if the challenge is successful to have the data erased, rectified, completed or amended.  

_**Terms and Conditions of Membership.**_

Each subscriber should carefully read each of the terms and conditions of membership of this site. By accepting membership to this site you are unconditionally accepting all of those terms and conditions. Some of those terms and conditions may also affect the right of this site to use information that it has gathered from subscribers.

In the event of any conflicts between the membership terms and conditions and this privacy policy statement, the provisions of this privacy policy shall control.
